

PROFILE

- ✓ nguyenduymanh241196@gmail.com
- **©** 0942627196 / 0559412132
- manh.com.vn
- Hai Boi, Dong Anh, Ha noi, Viet Nam

SKILLS

OFFICE

- Able to use tools like Word, Excel, Power Point.
- Automate tasks using VBA

FOREIGN LANGUAGE

- EnglishScore certificate: CEFR B1
- · Good ability to read, understand and translate technical documents in English. Communicate English is at a good level

MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

- · Good skills in using 3D design software such as NX, SolidWork, AutoCad,...
- Able to use Festo Fluidsim compressed air simulation software as well as components to support pneumatic system design calculations
- · CAE preprocessing tool: ANSA.
- Software for simulation and analysis of CAE results: VCollab
- · Read, understand and edit drawings and technical documents
- Design, assemble, and repair automatic machinery systems

PROCESS AUTOMATION

- Python, Javascript, VBA (excel,powerpoint), HTML, CSS.
- Framework: Node.js, Express.js.
- · Database: MongoDB, MySQL Workbenches...

NGUYEN DUY MANH

MECHANICAL ENGINEER

OBJECTIVE

Mechanical Engineer with over 5 years of experience in design, assembly, product development and process automation looking for a mechanical engineer position related to design, simulation, optimization of process automation to drive design innovation and increase operational efficiency.

EDUCATION



MAJOR: MECHANICAL ENGINEERING // 8/2014 - 8/2019

Ha noi University of Science and Technology

Major: Mechanical and Manufacturing Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE



MECHANICAL DESIGNER // 9/2018 - 2/2019

ROBOCON 2019 BK STAR Group

- Directly participating in layout design and construction of the Robocon field.
- · Design the lifting system, push system, supporting frame structure for the robot.
- TECHNICAL STAFF // 7/ 2019 3/2020

SHIOGAI SEIKI VIETNAM CO., LTD

- Participating in the design and assembly of the "tape eraser production line" for Plus company
- Design, make 2D drawings, quote and assemble spring winding machines, Semiautomatic Chamfering Machine

PRODUCTION MACHINE ENGINEER // 9/2020 - 12/2021

TERUMO VIETNAM CO., LTD

- · Participating in the improvement and manufacture of a solvent supply system to separate the mold for the (RFC end processing machine).
- · Participating in the process of transferring machine technology from Japan related to Radifocus Glidecath products.
- · Research manufacture jigs, installation jigs to support equipment as well as worker's manipulation to increase productivity.

CAD/CAE ENGINEER // 2/2022 - Now

FPT SOFTWARE COMPANY LIMITED

- · Recreate CAD data, create pre-CAE data: create meshes, attach connections, materials and render force,... using ANSA software.
- Use VCollab, Animator,... to measure forces, simulate, reproduce deformation, collect data and analysis to evaluate results.
- Automate the data collection and processing process using Python, VBA (excel) Create your own tools works on ANSA software to optimize tasks using Python.
- Data CRUD tasks on the customer's internal website: timesheets, management meeting schedule, web scraping,... using Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, python.
- Create the company's internal web interface using the framework: Ant Design, JS, html, css. © topcv.vn